# Jan Werbrouck | Graphics Programmer

#### janwerbrouck2000@gmail.com

+44 7544 79 75 32

+32 487 55 10 44

# About me

Hi, I am Jan. 22 years old. I grew up in Belgium and I started programming about 4 years ago when I started my higher education in Game Development. My main interests are graphics programming, writing shaders and optimisation. I have a lot of curiosity and I am always open to learning new skills.

#### **Relevant Skills**

- · C++
- · DirectX 11/12
- · Vulkan
- · GLSL
- · HLSL

- · C#
- · Unity
- · Unreal Engine C++ & Blueprints
- · Pix, NSight, RenderDoc

# Experience

### JUNIOR PROGRAMMER | SEPTEMBER 2021 - CURRENT | CLIMAX STUDIOS

Worked as a part of the graphics team of an undisclosed AAA Title for Sony in Unreal Engine. This included adding new material nodes, fixing shader issues, profiling and optimising rendering and memory issues.

Currently working on the optimisation team for another AAA Title for Microsoft, profiling and optimising the game for Xbox.

#### Internship | Februari 2021 - June 2021 | Climax Studios

Programming in Unreal Engine C++ and implementing multiplayer functionality for an early prototype in Unreal Engine. Also worked on an undisclosed AAA Title for Sony.

#### STUDENT JOB | I-SOLV-IT

(<u>joris@isolvit.be</u> | +32 484 95 86 46)

Working on Windows applications, using **SQL**, **C**# and **WPF**.

#### **Education**

## DIGITAL ARTS AND ENTERTAINMENT | 2018 - 2021 | HOWEST - KORTRIJK

· Professional Bachelor in Game Development

# Languages

- Dutch Native
- **English** Fluent (C2)